Guide to the Donald W. Baker College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection, 1950- 1969.
Baker, Donald W. College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection
- Dr. Benson and 2 unidentified men (Box 3, Folder VPC.00577)
  Description: Dr. (Kenneth?) Benson and 2 unidentified men standing in front of a truck. Benson is in the middle holding a box that reads "Haver-Glover Laboratories." There's a tractor in the background.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 10" x 10", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Douglas Charles Blood, 1960 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00578)
  Description: Candid of Douglas C. Blood talking to someone at the 52nd Annual Conference. Peter Kennedy is visible in the background
  Size and Number of Photographs: "6"" x 6.5"" 7.5"" x 9""", 2 prints on paper
- Unidentified student with intestines, 1963 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00579)
  Description: Unidentified student examining intestines in the lab. Same man pictured in VPC.00580
- Unidentified student holding hose, 1963 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00580)
  Description: Unidentified student holding hose in the lab. Same man is pictured in VPC.00579
- Veterinarians on a train, ca. 1940s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00581)
  Description: Veterinarians on a train (presumably) on their way to a conference. The conductor is visible in the rear.
- Veterinarians on a train, ca. 1940s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00582)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Bruckner and others on a train (presumably) on their way to a conference. The conductor is taking tickets
- Drs. Batchelder, Lowe, and Bixby, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00583)
  Description: Candid of (Left to Right) Roger Batchelder, Class of 1946; Jack Lowe, Class of 1956, and Donald Bixby, Class of 1935. They are standing in a group wearing suits. Batchelder is wearing a bow tie and holding a cigar.
- Donald Bixby and unidentified man, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00584)
  Description: Donald Bixby, class of 1935, and unidentified man standing outside in a doorway. The unidentified man is wearing a cardigan sweater.
- Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00585)
  Description: Dr. Donald Bixby, Class of 1935, and farmer carrying a milk can numbered 135.
- Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00586)
  Description: Donald Bixby, class of 1935, standing with an unidentified farmer in front of a car in his coveralls. Bixby is holding a clipboard.
- Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00587)
  Description: Donald Bixby, class of 1935, standing with an unidentified farmer in front of a car in his coveralls. Bixby is holding a clipboard. The door of the car is open. The farmer is wearing a plaid wool coat.
- Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00588)
  Description: Donald Bixby, class of 1935, standing with an unidentified farmer outside a barn. Bixby is standing in the doorway. There is an "American Agriculturist" sign above his head.
- Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00589)
  Description: Donald Bixby, class of 1935, standing with an unidentified farmer in front of a car in the street. Same farmer is pictured in VPC.00590.
- Unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00590)
  Description: Unidentified farmer standing behind a car. Same farmer is pictured in VPC.00589.
- Unidentified farmer and child, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00591)
  Description: Unidentified farmer and child. Behind the farmers head is an "American Agriculturist" sign and a "Farm Bureau sign.
- Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00592)
  Description: Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer standing in front of a barn and behind a car. Bixby is holding a clipboard and looking a the camera
  Size and Number of Photographs:, 1 print on paper
- Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00593)
  Description: Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer standing in front of a barn and behind a car. Bixby looking down at his clipboard.
- Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00594)
  Description: Donald Bixby and unidentified farmer standing in front of a car in the snow. Bixby is leaning on the open door and wearing sunglasses.
- Donald O. Bixby and unidentified farmer, ca. 1950s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00595)
  Description: Candid of Donald Bixby, class of 1935, and unidentified farmer. Bixby is reading a paper from a clipboard in the field.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4.5" x 9", 1 print on cardboard (cropped)
- Unidentified man with bull, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00596)
  Description: Unidentified man with a bull. He's wearing a hat and a cut-off plaid shirt.
- Robert Schirmer and John Wheat, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00597)
  Description: Candid of Robert G. Schirmer, class of 1946 and John D. Wheat, class of 1945. Both are wearing suits. One is facing the camera with his hands clasped in front of him.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 10", 1 print on cardboard
- W. D. Evans, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00598)
  Description: Candid of W. D. Evans, class of 1964, kneeling with a sheep. The sleeve of the left arm of his coveralls is torn off.
- John H. Fudens, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00599)
  Description: Candid of John H Fudens, class of 1964 kneeling with a sheep. See also VPC.00424.
- Dr. Willoughby and unidentified man, 1963 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00600)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Willoughby from Ontario and unidentified man examining specimens in trays in the lab.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7.5"" x 8"" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dr. Avery Smith and parents, 1964 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00601)
  Description: Dr. Avery Smith, class of 1964 and his parents at commencement. He is holding his robes.
- Unidentified woman with chihuahua, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00602)
  Description: Unidentified woman holding a chihuahua. There are two unidentified boys and one unidentified man with her. The unidentified man could be Dr. Bull.
- Dr. Dorothy Bradley, ca. 1940s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00603)
  Description: Dr. Dorothy Bradley Smallridge, class of 1943, with a sheep
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7.5"" x 10.5"" 2"" x 3""", 1 print on cardboard 1 print on paper
- Class of 1965 students in the library, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00604)
  Description: 11 members of the class of 1965 gathered around a table in the library. There are coffee cups on the table. One student in the center is reading the Journal of Parisitology.
- Unidentified man and Dr. William F. Tierney, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00605)
  Description: Dr. William F. Tierney, Class of 1935, and unidentified man standing outside near a parking lot. Tierney is on the right. Unidentified man is wearing a hat.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 6", 1 print on particle board
- Dr. Fehr and Dr. Merry, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00606)
  Description: Dr. F.F. Fehr and Dr. A.E. Merry, class of 1906, standing outside facing each other.
- Charles Rife, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00607)
  Description: Charles Rife, class of 1925, looking to his left. He is standing in front of curtains. He is talking to someone taller who is cropped out of the picture.
- Southern Tier Veterinary Medical Association Auxiliary, 1962 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00608)
  Description: "Southern Tier Veterinary Medical Association Auxiliary. Seated, left to right: Mrs. Lincoln E. Field, Mrs. D. W. Baker, Mrs. D. Sherwood, Mrs. Richard Guthrie, Mrs. Peter Olfason, unidentified woman, Mrs. Rudolph Steffen, and Mrs. S. J. Roberts Standing"
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7" 7.5" x 9.5", "8 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Class in Farriery with Jean Layton, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00609)
  Description: Farriery class, looks like continuing education. Jean Layton is in the center. The building is probably the Livestock Pavilion on Judd Falls Road.
- M. R. Clarkson, 1965 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00610)
  Description: Candid of M. R. Clarkson, wearing glasses and a bow tie
- Mrs. Poppensiek, Mrs. Clarkson, Dr. Clarkson, 1965 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00611)
  Description: Left to right candid of Mrs. Poppensiek, Mrs. Clarkson, M. R. Clarkson and Edgar "Brud" Tucker. All of them are wearing coats. It appears to be an Annual Conference event.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9" 7"" x 6"" 3" x 5", 3 prints on cardboard (cropped), 1 print on paper
- Leonard Goss, ca.1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00612)
  Description: Portrait of Leonard Goss, Class of 1938
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 7", 1 print on cardboard
- Joseph B. Engle and Lawrence Goodman, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00613)
  Description: Candid of Joseph B. Engle and Lawrence Goodman, both class of 1926. Goodman is wearing a tie with a horse on it. Engle is wearing a bow tie.
- Aubrey A. Wooden inspects a mangy cow, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00614)
  Description: Aubrey A. Wooden, Class of 1923, inspects a mangy cow
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 7.5", 1 print on paper
- Audrey Empson, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00615)
  Description: Audrey Empson holding teacup. Dr. Fincher is visible in the background
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 7.5" x 9.5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- J. R. Smith, W. S. Newman, Fred Schutz, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00616)
  Description: From left to right: J. R. Smith; William S. Newman, Class of 1907; and Fred Schutz, Class of 1933. They are holding a picture of Newman as a member of the crew team
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper"
- C. A. "Pop" Lueder receiving award, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00617)
  Description: From left to right: J.R Smith; C. A. "Pop" Lueder, Class of 1902; Mrs. Lueder; and Fred Schutz, Class of 1933. They are holding a picture of Lueder as a member of the crew team.
- Drs. Newman, Lueder and Van Orman, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00618)
  Description: Left to right: William Seymour Newman, Class of 1907; Charles Augustus "Pop" Lueder, Class of 1902; and Ray Van Orman, Class of 1908. Names are printed on print.
- Annual Conference group in a lecture hall, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00619)
  Description: Annual Conference group in a lecture hall. John Bentinck-Smith is visible in the second row, far right. Caption under same shot featured in VPC.00620 reads: "Profile of the Yankee Veterinarian." Caption under particle board print reads, "Refresher Course.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 9", 7" x 9", 1 print on paper
- Composite, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00620)
  Description: Composite of VPC.00616, VPC.00617, and VPC.00619.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 8" x 14", 5 prints on paper
- William J. Donawick, three unidentified students, and a cow, 1962 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00621)
  Description: William J. Donawick, Class of 1963, and 3 unidentified students examining a calf's teeth outside. Same scene pictured in VPC.00630.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "6.5"" x 7.5"" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Arthur E. Scheld and Robert L. Westbrook, 1962 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00622)
  Description: Arthur E. Scheld and Robert L. Westbrook, both Class of 1963, examining a specimen in the lab. Scheld is on the left.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Mrs. Fred Schultz, 1965 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00623)
  Description: Mrs. Fred Schultz at a party, probably an Annual Conference event.
- Dr. and Mrs. Fred Schultz, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00624)
  Description: Dr. and Mrs. Fred Schultz, Class of 1933. She is wearing a coat and hat.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 9", 1 print on paper
- Mrs. Fred Schultz, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00625)
  Description: Mrs. Fred Schultz standing in a kitchen near a sink. She is wearing pearls.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 2 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- H. H. Dukes, 1956 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00626)
  Description: Candid of H. H. Dukes at a podium on Honor Day.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 10", 2 prints on paper
- Dr. and Mrs. H. H. Dukes, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00627)
  Description: Dr. and Mrs. H. H. Dukes. Mrs. Dukes is carrying flowers
- Dr.s Dukes and Rankin, 1960 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00628)
  Description: H. H. Dukes, Class of 1918, and A. D. Rankin, Class of 1939. Dukes is in the foreground and is partially obscured by a plant. His portrait is on the wall behind him.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7"" x 6.5"" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Irwin H. Roberts, 1964 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00629)
  Description: Candid of Irwin H. Roberts, class of 1937, from Albuquerque, New Mexico, at the 101st AVMA conference in Chicago
- William J. Donawick, three unidentified students, and a cow, 1962 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00630)
  Description: William J. Donawick, Class of 1963, and 3 unidentified students examining a calf's teeth outside. Same scene pictured in VPC.00621.
- Kenneth Benson and three unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00631)
  Description: Kenneth Benson, class of 1948, and three unidentified men. Benson is standing in the middle with his back to the camera. The man on the right is leaning on a chair. Same event is pictured in VPC.00249
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 2 print on paper"
- Richard L. Fortune, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00632)
  Description: Richard L. Fortune, class of 1935, standing, arms akimbo, in a plaid shirt, facing the camera.
- R. E. Fuechsel, M. Zimmerman, H. L. Szlachta, and J.C. Siegrist, ca. 1950 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00633)
  Description: "4 students posing outside. Left to right: Robert E. Fuechsel, Manuel Zimmerman, Henry L. Szlachta, Jacob C. Siegrist, all class of 1950."
- Mrs. John McAuliff, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00634)
  Description: Candid of Mrs. John McAuliff waving at the camera. She is wearing pearls, glasses and a corsage.
- John McAuliff, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00635)
  Description: John L. McAuliff, Class of 1918, inoculating a cow. He is wearing sunglasses and a bow tie.
- Louis Corwin, S. J. Roberts, Joseph B. Engle, H. Noonan, 1949 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00636)
  Description: "Posed shot of (left to right): Louis Corwin, class of 1919; Stephen Roberts, class of 1938; Joseph B. Engle, class of 1926; and Henry Patrick ""Pat"" Noonan, class of 1919. According to Neg envelope, the event was the 1949 Annual Conference."
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5", 2 prints on cardboard
- Drs. Ranney, Roberts and Matuszak, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00637)
  Description: Albert F. Ranney, Class of 1932, Stephen J Roberts, Class of 1938, and Walter J Matuszak, Class of 1943. Ranney and Matuszak are shaking hands.
- Stephen J. Roberts, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00638)
  Description: Stephen J. Roberts, class of 1938, at a desk on the phone.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 9", 1 print on paper
- Drs. Field, Bell, and Roberts, 1965 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00639)
  Description: Posed shot of (left to right): Lincoln Field, class of 1930, Wilson Bell, class of 1939; and S. J. Roberts, class of 1938. Appears to be an Annual Conference event where a chair was given as a gift. See also VPC.00467 and VPC.00640.
- Drs. Field, Bell, De Camp, and Roberts, 1965 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00640)
  Description: Posed shot of (left to right): Lincoln Field, class of 1930, Wilson Bell, class of 1939; Clayton E. De Camp, Class of 1924; and S. J. Roberts, class of 1938. Appears to be an Annual Conference event where a chair was given as a gift. See also VPC.00639 an
- Lincoln E. Field, 1960 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00641)
  Description: Candid of Lincoln E. Field smoking a pipe at a race track with an unidentified man and woman.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 3" x 5", 2 prints on paper (one cropped)
- Richard Guthrie and Lincoln Field, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00642)
  Description: Richard Guthrie and Lincoln Field, both class of 1930. Field is wearing a hat with a bandana around the crown.
- Lincoln Field, S.J. Roberts and others watching a film, 1962 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00643)
  Description: Lincoln Field, S.J. Roberts and others watching a film. Probably an Annual Conference event
- Jack Lowe, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00644)
  Description: Jack Lowe, Class of 1956, with a flock of sheep in a barn
- Jack and Audrey Lowe, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00645)
  Description: Candid of Jack and Audrey Lowe standing in the foyer in front of James Law Auditorium, just about to get their name tags at a conference. She is wearing a tiny hat with a veil and pearls.
- Dr. Albert F. Ranney and unidentified man., ca. 1960s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00646)
  Description: Dr. Albert F. Ranney, Class of 1932, and unidentified man. Ranney is leaning on a table, wearing glasses. Glass if water to his left.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4.5" x 8", 1 print on cardboard (cropped)
- Dr. Arnold E. Hilbert, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00647)
  Description: Candid of Arnold E. Hilbert, Class of 1927
  Size and Number of Photographs: "5.5"" x 7.5"" 8"" x 10", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Bruce Widger, 1960 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00648)
  Description: Bruce Widger, Class of 1951, at a New York State Veterinary Medical Society meeting
- Bruce Widger and wife and article, 1964 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00649)
  Description: Candid of Bruce Wider and his wife at Commencement. One print includes a news article about the election of Bruce Widger to the Board of Trustees
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 11", 2 prints on cardboard
- Dr. and Mrs. Robert Fuess, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00650)
  Description: Dr. and Mrs. Robert Fuess, class of 1952, shucking oysters or clams at a picnic.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9", 3 prints on cardboard
- Mrs. Robert Fuess and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00651)
  Description: Mrs. Robert Fuess and unidentified man husking corn for a picnic.
- Dr. and Mrs. Charles Fletcher, 1960 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00652)
  Description: Dr. and Mrs. Charles Fletcher, class of 1932 at a formal event. She is holding a fur wrap and her purse. He is wearing a tuxedo and holding his glasses.
- Dr. and Mrs. Chamberlain, 1955 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00653)
  Description: Dr. and Mrs. Kenneth W. Chamberlain, Class of 1952, at the 47th Annual Conference
- Drs. McClelland and Shaffer, 1953 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00654)
  Description: Robert B. McClelland, Class of 1934, and Joseph C. Shaffer, Class of 1945 at a New York State Veterinary Medical Society clambake. They are outside shaking hands.. One has a glass of beer in his hand and a cigar in his mouth. Published in Ellis Leonard, "
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 6", 1 print on cardboard
- Lyle Compton and 2 unidentified people, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00655)
  Description: Candid of Lyle Compton, class of 1931 and 2 unidentified people at a dinner table presumably at a conference. Woman in the middle is wearing a satin jacket.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 8", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Robert W. Kirk, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00656)
  Description: Robert W. Kirk, class of 1946 running across a field.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 8" 2"" x 8""", 1 print on paper
- Croshaw, Loomis, Mc Auliff, Greenwood, Hoff, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00657)
  Description: Posed shot of Ellis Croshaw, class of 1953, W. K. Loomis, class of 1952, John L. McAuliff, class of 1918, A. R. Greenwood, class of 1952, and E. J. Hoff Jr, class of 1952
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9"x 12", 1 print on paper
- Norman Pick, A. Martin Simensen, and Edward H. Fallon, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00658)
  Description: Norman Pick, A. Martin Simensen, and Edward H. Fallon, all Class of 1956, at an Annual Conference
- Afternoon party, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00659)
  Description: An afternoon party at the home of James A. Baker, on Snyder Hill in Ithaca.
- James A. Baker, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00660)
  Description: James A. Baker seated wearing a vest on a plane. There is a pack of cigarettes on table
- James A. Baker, 1961 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00661)
  Description: James A. Baker sitting with legs crossed on a plane.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9" 5" x 7", 2 prints on cardboard
- James A. Baker, 1961 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00662)
  Description: Candid of James A. Baker seated on a plane, smoking a cigarette. He is talking to Peter Olafson, who is facing away from the camera.
- Peter Olafson, 1961 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00663)
  Description: Candid of Peter Olafson and unidentified man on a plane
  Size and Number of Photographs: 3" x 5" 4"" x 6"" 8" x 10", 3 prints on paper, two cropped
- Vets on a train, ca. 1950s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00664)
  Description: Vets on a train to a conference. In the front is a man and a woman--both are not smiling. Woman is wearing a hat and a light cardigan. Behind them is Peter Olafson. See also VPC.00668.
- Peg Catlin Leonard at Peter Olafson's door, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00665)
  Description: Margaret " Peg" Catlin Leonard, Class of 1940, at Peter Olafson's door during reunion. Sign on the door reads, "Notice: To Visiting Alumni(ae) - Gone (but not forgotten) to Israel - Will Return in 1 Yr. - Best Regards, Peter Olafson."
- Peter Olafson and unidentified woman, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00666)
  Description: Peter Olafson and unidentified woman sitting at a conference table, looking right, and laughing at a speaker.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 6", 1 print on paper
- Herbert L. Bandemer and Peter Olafson, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00667)
  Description: Herbert L. Bandemer, Class of 1955, and Peter Olafson, Class of 1926. Olafson is standing with arms akimbo
  Size and Number of Photographs: "10"" x 10"" 8" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 transparency"
- Vets on a train, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00668)
  Description: Vets on a train to a conference. In the front is a man and a woman--both are not smiling. Woman is wearing a hat and a light cardigan. Behind them is Peter Olafson. See also VPC.00664.
- Vets on a train, ca. 1950s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00669)
  Description: Unidentified veterinarians on a train (presumably) on the way to a conference--1 bald man on left with light coat on, on the right a man blinking. Woman behind them. "Sigma Xi" written on negative
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Clive McCay and Steward Wright, ca. 1950s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00670)
  Description: Clive McCay and Steward Wright on a train.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 10", 3 prints on paper
- Veterinarians on a train, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00671)
  Description: Unidentified veterinarians on a train (presumably) on their way to a conference
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 7.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified veterinarians on a train, ca. 1950s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00672)
  Description: Unidentified veterinarians on a train (presumably) on the way to a conference. 3 are pictured: A woman looking to her left, a man also looking left--both are smiling. A man behind them also looking left, not smiling
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 8", 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified veterinarians on a train, ca. 1950s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00673)
  Description: Unidentified veterinarians on a train (presumably) on the way to a conference--4 pictured prominently. 2 in the front are both looking slightly to the right. 2 behind them. One is looking hard left, other is blinking
- Baker, Oalfson, Danks and Fincher, 1965 (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00674)